终于来了  终于来了
It's here! It's here.
我的未来终于来到了
My future is here.
我的未来就在这儿
My future is here!
夹在两片面包的中间
Between two slices of bread.
你的未来还早着呢
Your future can wait.
天啊
Look.
这不就是《太空狼人》里的道具服么
That's the costume from "space werewolves."
《太空狼人》可是一部一鸣惊人的动作电影
"Space werewolves" is a big action blockbuster
就像是下一部《暮光之城》一样
that's gonna be kind of like the next "twilight,"
除了主角是太空中的狼人而非地球上的吸血鬼
except it's werewolves in space instead of vampires on earth.
这个的可信度要高多了
It's way more believable.
所以  你得到了领衔主演的位置
So, you got the lead in the movie.
还没有  其实导演组认为一个姑娘看起来不够坚强
No. They actually don't think a girl will look tough enough.
所以你偷走了戏服
So you stole the suit
这样他们就拍不成电影了
so they can't make the movie.
你就这么心术不正啊
You are diabolical.
事实上  我跟他们说了要把狼人戏服寄给我
Actually, I talked them into sending me the werewolf suit
这样我就能拍照片来证明他们想错了
so I can take pictures in it to prove them wrong.
这样也成啊
That could work too.
我更喜欢心术不正的你
I like you better diabolical.
丽芙  大好消息
Liv, great news.
电视台第四频道刚打来电话
Channel four just called.
这周五他们要到咱家里
They're coming to the house this Friday
专门采访你
to interview you
来做他们的早间烹饪节目
for their morning news cooking segment.
我要上《尼比斯私房菜》了
I'm doing "Nibbling with Nimbus"?
对的 简直不敢相信
Yes. Can you believe it?
我爱死那个节目了
I love that segment.
上周  尼比斯和范·迪塞尔一起油炸了一只火鸡
Last week, nimbus deep fried a Turkey with Vin Diesel.
（范·迪塞尔：美国电影演员，制片人）
等等  妈妈  你刚刚说的是周五么
Wait, mom, did you say Friday?
又是《太空狼人》摄影
So a "space werewolves" movie photo shoot
又是一个直播电视访谈
and a live TV interview.
好了  这一周赶通告压力大咯
Okay, this is shaping up to be an oddly stressful week.
但是  幸亏你有一个超级酷的妈妈
Well, luckily you have a super-cool mom
还是一个可以帮你应付一切压力的治疗师
who's also a therapist. And she can help you manage your stress.
太好了  因为我马上需要你的帮助
Good. Because I am going to need your help
帮我挑出最上镜的那套衣服
picking out a TV-rrific outfit.
你需要我的时尚建议
You want my fashion advice.
天啊  这一天终于到来了
Oh, it's finally happening.
那好
Okay.
一件农妇衫
How about a peasant blouse
外加一条紧身裤怎么样
with some sensible trousers?
果然 找你要建议大错特错了
Yeah, this was a mistake.